being flexible means to shape it how you
want it every employee is a unique
individual with their own needs so
you'll need a flexible employee benefits
program that allows employees to
customize their benefit package based on
their needs and fits within their HR
budget
Prudential has designed a seamless
One-Stop platform to make benefits
claims easy while engaging employees
with rewards and recognition they can
now select their preferred level of
coverage with their voluntary benefits
for each of their group Insurance
components crew benefits Flex converts
to these voluntary benefits to points
which employees can use to make flexible
spending claims or redeem e-vouchers in
our digital Marketplace through benefits
Flex comes built with other exciting
rewards and recognition functions where
employees can earn points via
appreciation from others special
occasions and even attending corporate
events with Pro benefits Flex we'll do
the heavy lifting so you don't have to
contact us today to find out more
[Music]